welcome to the center of the baseball world tonight
it's one of the world powers
japan taking on one of the big surprises in this tournament
in team mexico
here we go and all eyes on rokiki sasaki
you're thinking fastball
all the way
it's fastball
and then adjust rea strikes out swinging one
oh two well
mexico has their hands full
that's for sure
that's the first batter
and that's what he was throwing
what makes you go
patrick sandoval
a teammate for show hao toni well
this is a guy who's gonna mix it up
that slider change up
but throws thirty seven percent fastball rate
i don't think this is the bait pitch right here
not so much an action pitch
it worked
oh
that was nasty right there in it
that's the way he's going to pitch today
japan's got their hands full and strike the ball
got the call on the outside corner for looking nice right now
and so it's full on otani on a payoff pitch
so tony watches strike three
and how about patrick sandoval here in the first
the savees a bunch of big hits for mexico in this world
baseball classic that was lying down to leon
reveal that that's gonna be a hit
so the first two of the game comes from isaac
a one out single with luis as standing in another one too maria
hit the picture
maybe right in the midsection
and as will be safe
at first sounds like a punch to the stomach
i think i think he's gonna be okay
though yeah
that's gonna hurt
it's gonna leave a bruise
but i think he'll be okay
two on one out
no score in the second
last ball on should be two
there's one for the first
a double play
a gut punch to roki sasaki
but he gets up off the turf and retires
aside from masaaka
yoshida had a great tournament so far
he hits that one on the line
back up the middle base hit
so the first hit for japan
the yoshida with a lead off single
and that's a good piece of hitting right there
taking what sandoval gave him with that
change up up in the zone
because of what a big star is
chopper is short
the flick
the second
that's one for the first
scouting
double play
what a turn
with the first baseman okamoto running just enough time to turn that ground ball
and into two outs
one hit
nobody left roddy
tellez
oh two
he's in a pickle right here
big hole on the ground and nobody's there at third
he beats the shift with a ground ball
well
that's a really good two strike approach
right there look
how he hits
this
just gets on top of it
doesn't try to do too much to have finish
had a base hit his first time up to two
it's a little pop up behind third
and it's gonna fall
they where kami picked it up off the bouts
so saki came over to cover
so that for telus to stop at second
but back to back two out hits
a team that gets base hits with two outs more than now
becomes the team that wins the game
big moment here
oh one
maria to
what a moment he got the hanging splitter for a base hit
in the first stop at hanging splitter again for homer
biggest hit of his young career
and it's three nothing mexico with the way patrick sandoval is pitching
he's faced the minimum through three innings
that one on the ground in the right field base hit
so condo comes through with the second hit of the game for japan
and there will be a base runner on for otony
tony lights one to left center field
it's going to be caught by thomas
yoshida who has a base hit already
oh two
that one is landed the left piece here
so yoshi is two for two
and japan is threatening
just a couple of careless sliders right there up in the zone
especially o two
these pitches cannot be at the top of the zone
when you got them basically dominated too good of a hitter for that
they'll take what
they can get absolute rocket to left center for a base hit
and this is a very big bad for a big star in japan
see the smile from yoshida
but you know
tao or ami has not been smiling much in this tournament
he's the mvp two time mvp triple crown winner
but four for eighteen without a home run
now the one two two three just could not get the swing off a shutdown
ednow on the mount for team japan
yoshinobu
yamamoto
it's a soft bouncer
the second throw the first and plenty of time for our number three
so yamamoto comes into the game and retires mexico without a run
patrick sandoval has been excellent
he misses with his first pitch of the end into kazuma okamoto oomoto
a high fly ball
deep left field
a rosa arena at the wall
he leaps
are you not entertained
this guy
he just proved to everybody that
yeah
he had the baseball
wow
what a catch
sets himself up
sees the wall
takes a peek and says
okay
here we go lift off
it's the only thing he hadn't done yet
he's made a great catch
now he's robbed a home run
he is something else left hand to pop like that
it's just impressive
how the ball just jumps off his bat
oh too
he winds that one in the left field
and that's going to be a hit for a time
from one star to another
rosa a picks it up
and tony trying to help get his team going another opportunity
third inning in a row where japan's offense
putting big pressure on mexico
the one one that one is hit down the left field line
but rosa a on the move
the rosa a will get there and make it
they left two men on base in the fourth inning
they left three on base in the fifth
they left three on base in the sixth and another opportunity here
this one comes with two down
now
the two two
it is hit high and deep down the right field line toward the corner
it is is gone off the foul pole tie game
japan biggest game
elimination game
they've answered
the urgency was put to test
they're alive
what a moment
what a moment for yoshida
he went back to the changer
a little bit full
but man
those lefties you throw them down
and in it's set up for randy rosa a
that one is like right here
going back quickly and over the head of up against the wall
a rosa arena in the second
with a one out double
you want to talk about bat speed
randy rosa arena has just displayed it
and the go ahead run is in scoring position for alex verdugo
left center field that's gonna be a hit
and mexico is gonna go back ahead
the rosa is in the score
verdugo with a double
it's four to three isaac paz two for three
has been a huge part of the mexican offense
two and one on the ground basin in the left field
here comes manassas to throw the tag
got him at the plane
but another run for mexico
after the rally for japan to tie the game
a two running
i sacrificing time
yeah
because you got the guy who's got the broken finger again
those already given it up
got to get it down
he butts and he does get it down
vanessence look
but take the throw to first
and almost a disaster
as came over to cover
and the throw was a little offline
but they do get the out
that one is driven to left field
but rosa arena will make a catch
knocking
he'll come into score
the throw goes to third
it's a one run game
another hard hit ball
tracked down by rosa arena and got the job done
got the run in
gets that fastball right there up
the zone
makawa was putting on a display and batting practice today
by the way
simplifies the approach
hits the job done
trying to keep this a one run game with tony
do up in the bottom of the ninth inning
fly ball shallow left falling
and it'll be
not an easy play
so many things happening
going back on the ball
you got the left field
they're coming
you got to tell them
you've got it right at the last minute
pop your glove out
and hopefully you got lucky and again a got lucky
so here we go bottom of the night
oh tony
tonight has lined out
singled
walked after striking out
looking all the way back to the first inning
oh tony
rips a base hit in the right center field
head to the gap
cut off by thomas in center field of tony
stops its second with a lead off double
i was a preset
determined swing
taking what galambos was gonna give him
he sat on a pitch in the change up
and he got it
and boy he delivered
and now masa taka yoshida
who hit the home run to tie the game
his last time up
he could win it with a home run here
very high ball for shoot to be the pitch runner for yoshida
japan is playing to win this game
right here
right now
yukio shutto the winning run
una taka murakami just has not looked comfortable at the plate at all
he's been thinking about this moment for six years now
he's too good
too good
even if he hasn't looked great tonight
he goes looks back at otani
the pitch is hit to left field and very well
and it is a tony flying around third
right behind him
scoring the winning run
it's a walk off
japan will play for the championship
be thinking about it for six years now
a moment in the world baseball classic
he will never forget a country that is going absolutely crazy in japan